<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Guide for Winner</string>
    <string name="app_name_for_title">Guide for Mini Militia Doodle gun</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello World!</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="book1title">About Mini Militia Doodle gun</string>
    <string name="book1body">Mini Militia is an online and offline 2D shooter, released back in 2011 for iOS and 2015 for Android. According to reports, it was listed as one of the top games in India for the year 2017.
        \n\n

Although the game is pretty simple and easy to play, for new players, it can be hard as they don’t know much about how to play the game. So, Here are some tips and tricks for you while you play Mini Militia!</string>
    <string name="book_1_title">Never Combat with Pros</string>
    <string name="book_1_body">
        If you are a newbie or an amateur, then it is best for you that you avoid getting into combat with a pro who has high scores. Pro Players have a lot of experience and for starters, they are hard to beat and it is not an easy thing to combat against them.
        \n
        \n

        If you have some skills then you should try out your luck, but buy a pro pack first in-order to use dual weapons and have a better chance against them.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_2_title">Never Combat with Hackers</string>
    <string name="book_2_body">Hackers are cowards and they are found in almost every game. They kill the essence of the game and ruin everything. If you combat hackers then you will not enjoy the game and rather you would like to uninstall the game. They are using the hack and have unlimited strength and are hard to kill. It’s better to just avoid combating with them.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_3_title">Choose a Powerful Gun</string>
    <string name="book_3_body">
        While combating one of the things that can help you greatly against your rivals is a powerful gun. Always try to choose a powerful gun such as M16, Rocket Launcher or Rifles as they will let you kill the other players in one or two shots.
        \n
        \n
        If you are good at sniping, then it gives you an extra edge.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_4_title">Use a Shield</string>
    <string name="book_4_body">
        While in combat, it always a good choice to have something that can protect you from others killing you. When you use a Shield in Mini Militia, it will help you defend against the shooting from your enemies and will help you to survive longer.
        \n
        \n
        A combination of Shield with UZI or Revolver works best.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_5_title">Double Guns
</string>
    <string name="book_5_body">
       A combination of two guns will help you kill more people in the game and you will have a higher chance of getting a high rank.
        \n
        \n
        One of the best combinations in the game is Shotgun and Sniper. One can help you with a short range, while the latter can help you in the long range.
        \n
        \n
        Rifle and Sniper combination is also very useful. Try picking different combinations and choose which works best for you.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_6_title">Ammo Reload Time
</string>
    <string name="book_6_body">
        One of thing that is very annoying that in close when you are shooting and your ammo runs out then the enemy kills you and it is very annoying, especially for guns that have low ammo capacity.
        \n
        \n
        Therefore, it is important that before you encounter an enemy, make sure that your ammo is fully reloaded and try to aim at the enemy in order to preserve your bullets.
        \n
        \n

    </string>
    <string name="book_7_title">Nitro
</string>
    <string name="book_7_body">
        It is important that you try to main the nitro to full or near to full because when you encounter a powerful enemy and you just don’t have a powerful gun or are out of ammo, then you will be able to run away if you have full nitro. So, keep your nitro around full in order to escape from enemies when needed.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_8_title">Using Bombs and Grenades</string>
    <string name="book_8_body">
        Bombs and Grenades are an important part of the game and you should use them carefully. Try to place poison grenades in the area where enemies would spawn and it will kill them automatically.
        \n
        \n
        If they throw a grenade towards you, you can either send it back quickly or run away to save your life.
        \n
        \n

    </string>
    <string name="book_9_title">Switch Fist</string>
    <string name="book_9_body">
        During an encounter, if both you and your enemy run out of ammo then you should quickly switch over to fists and kill him with your hands.
        \n
        \n
        As he may be busy in reloading, while you can get close to him and kill your enemies with the fists.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_10_title">Suicide</string>
    <string name="book_10_body">
        If you don’t want your enemies to have more kills than you, then you should consider committing suicide.
        \n
        \n
        When your health is running low then it is better to commit suicide instead of being killed as suicide won’t give any kill points to your enemies.
        \n
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="book_11_title"></string>
    <string name="book_11_body"></string>

</resources>